hospitalityonline.com 2010-06-23

# Hospitality Online Privacy Policy

The purpose of your job search is to advance your personal career. Hospitality Online is committed to helping you advance your career while maintaining your privacy and the privacy of all others using Hospitality Online. 

Hospitality Online provides an interactive Internet site to enable hospitality industry job seekers to find career information, information about employers, and tips and techniques to help job seekers to succeed. Employers need the opportunity to present their jobs, company and properties completely and professionally. 

Employers have the opportunity to provide detailed profiles about their property/company to attract the best quality applicants. Employers can also provide very detailed information about jobs to help job seekers better identify jobs they are qualified for. 

Applicants and Employers wanted a different kind of job site, one that provided job seekers much more information about the employers, and a job site that provided them more information about jobs. Job seekers also didn't want to be bothered with information about jobs they were not interested in, that meant effective pre-screening. 

Providing more complete information during each step of the process means we have to collect more detailed information about job seekers and employers. 

The information you submit to Hospitality Online remains private. We compile statistics in many various ways, but we do not share statistics on any individual job seekers. Likewise we aggregate information from employers when we publish statistics. Last, we do not sell, rent, or exchange lists of job seekers or employers with other companies. 

We compile statistics such as the number of users visiting the site by time period, position, salary range, etc. Just as we compile statistics on the number of jobs advertised by position, salary range, area of the country, etc. 

Employers each have their own section on Hospitality Online. Those sections often include links to their Internet sites, online job applications, and resume submittal directions. When you respond to employers your information is going to them and is subject to their privacy policies. Hospitality Online is not responsible for the information that employers receive from you, whether through electronic transmission by Hospitality Online, or fax or mail transmissions you submit. 

Hospitality Online has alliances with other companies to provide additional services. Note that when you link to those other services you are going directly to those companies and you are subject to their privacy policies. 

Job seekers, employers, and others have the opportunity to share success stories and other comments with Hospitality Online, usually through e-mail. These comments become the property of Hospitality Online. We may use this information for marketing purposes, or to contact you for additional information or clarification. 

**Your information about you. (Job seekers)**  
Hospitality Online has a registration process to provide job seekers with their own private section within Hospitality Online. This also enables you to access features like the [Hospitality Online Career Toolkit](http://toolkit.hospitalityonline.com/) and provides tools to enable you to manage your career. Some of these sections request detailed information from you about your career and interests. You determine whether you participate or not, and at what level. 

The Hospitality Online Career Tool Kit is designed to streamline your career process, save you time, and present your qualifications very professionally, while allowing you to manage the entire process. 

Hospitality Online does not allow employers to search our database. When employers post jobs, those jobs are pre-screened against your objectives. When there is a match you are sent an e-mail alerting you to review the position the employer is advertising. If you are interested you respond directly to the employer. 

Hospitality Online does our best to make sure no one has unauthorized access to our database, but we can't guarantee that people won't gain access to our database without our consent. 

Once you have submitted your resume to an employer, we are not responsible for the privacy of your information. Once you have a new job, we strongly encourage you to send an e-mail to all companies you submitted your resume to. Tell them you have a new position and ask that they remove your resume from their files/database. 

**Credit Card Security**  
Hospitality Online uses a secure server for all credit card transactions. These credit card transactions use SSL encryption before being sent over the Internet. While we can't guarantee encryption or the privacy of your personal details and credit card transactions, SSL makes it very difficult for your information to be stolen or intercepted while the data is being transferred. 

**Cookies**  
To make things easier for you, Hospitality Online uses a feature called "Cookies." This enables file(s) to be transferred from a web site to the hard drive of your computer. Cookies make it easier for you and provides us statistics to improve Hospitality Online for you. 

Cookies are used to remember passwords, user names, to identify which pages, jobs, etc. are most visited, and for load balancing. They enable us to deliver service faster and to provide a more personalized experience for you. 

A Cookie will not permit a web site operator to learn any information to personally identify you, unless you have personally provided that information to the web site operator or you have set the preferences in your browser to provide this information. 

You can set your browser to reject cookies. Remember, if you de-activate the cookies feature in your browser it will disable access to certain features on Hospitality Online. 

**Third Party Links**  
Hospitality Online contains many links to other sites. We strongly encourage all employers and third parties to implement policies and procedures to protect the privacy of others. 

**Children**  
Hospitality Online does not collect information about children. We believe children should get their parents permission before giving out personal information. If you have concerns about your child's use of Hospitality Online go on the site with them to see how they are using Hospitality Online. Many students use Hospitality Online to collect information for school reports and to search for part-time or seasonal jobs. With your guidance Hospitality Online can be a very useful tool as they explore various careers. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
We review our privacy policy from time to time, and changes may occur. We ask that visitors review this Privacy Policy from time to time to be sure they are familiar with all sections. If you have questions, comments, or suggestions about our privacy practices please contact us at [privacy@hospitalityonline.com](mailto:privacy@hospitalityonline.com)
